Finding Aid for the John Lark Taylor Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
John Lark Taylor Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0434
5.04 linear_feet
The John Lark Taylor Papers contain correspondence, plays and original music by Taylor, photographs, promptbooks, playbills, radio scripts, and other stage and radio memorabilia spanning 1879 to 1944.
Scope and Content Note
The John Lark Taylor Papers contain correspondence, plays and original music by Taylor, photographs, promptbooks, playbills, radio scripts, and other stage and radio memorabilia spanning 1879 to 1944. The collection includes an autobiography by Taylor and an account of his season playing in Hamlet with John Barrymore.
John Lark Taylor bequeathed his collection of personal papers jointly to Peabody College and Vanderbilt University in 1946.
Biography
John Lark Taylor was born in Nashville, Tennessee in 1881. He attended Tarbox School and Fall Business College in Nashville before turning his attention to the stage.
As a teen, he played piano to accompany silent films in Nashville's first movie house. His first professional job was a $5/week vaudeville stint in St. Louis when he was 17 years old. The following year, he moved to New York and joined the Augustin Daly Stock Company. His first Broadway play was the Daly production of Taming of the Shrew with Tyrone Power, Sr. After Daly died in 1899, Taylor played with other stock companies in California and Nashville before returning to New York.
By 1906, Lark Taylor had joined the Sothern-Marlowe Company, and he played in theater productions for the company for the next 10 years. In 1922-1923, he played a part in the Arthur Hopkins' production of Hamlet with John Barrymore.
In 1924, Taylor sold his New York residence and moved back to Nashville with his mother. He started a Little Theater and began performing plays in a movie house near the Belcourt Theatre in Hillsboro Village. In 1933 he began doing radio programs for WSM, announcing broadcasts and performing in radio dramas. He continued his radio career until his retirement in 1942.
John Lark Taylor died on March 27, 1946 after a long illness.
- Biographical material; holograph autobiography; typescript autobiography (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- "My Season With John Barrymore in Hamlet (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Incoming (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Baggett, John F. (to WSM Radio) (1), 14 January 1935
  - Barton, S. W. (1), n.d.
  - Bircham, Lily (1), 6 November 1903
  - Blossom, E. C. (1), 6 May 1932
  - Brown, Gilmore (1), 19 March 1939
  - Burrus, Jefferson (1), n.d.
  - Clark, James E. (to WSM Radio) (1), 9 January 1935
  - Colyar, Mrs. George (1), n.d.
  - Cross, Amy (1), n.d.
  - Dave, E. H. (1), 10 August 1930
  - Davis, Mrs. Katie (1), n.d.
  - DePew, Marion (1), 28 October 1931
  - Elliott, Mrs. Annie Mary (1), 16 February 1932
  - Gerstenberg, Alice Erya (3), 20 January 1932, 28 January 1932, 30 January 1932
  - Gilbert, Rev. W. A. Harris, Sybil Jewett, Mrs. Henry Jones, Rebecca E. Kendall, Lucy May (1)
  - Kuhn, Casper B. Kyle, Howard (1), n.d.
  - McCloud, J. F. (to Mrs. Emma Taylor) (2), 30 June 1930, 19 November 1930 (1) 26 April 1930
  - Miller, Henry (3), 12 October 1934, 17 October 1934, 29 October 1934
  - Palmer, K. O. A. (1), n.d.
  - Pattison, Mrs. Leona (2), n.d., 28 March 1932 (1) 22 December 1931 (1) 8 December 1924
  - Riehl, Mildred (1), 23 February 1932
  - Short, George (1), n.d.
  - Smith, Mrs. Gilbert (1), n.d.
  - Snyder, Mary R. ("Carlotta") (3), n.d., 27 October 7, 4 March 1932
  - Wiggs, George W., (1) 17 May 1932
  - Williams, Mrs. Bessie (1), n.d.
  - Williams, Claude (1), n.d.
  - Incomplete Signatures
    - Bert (1), 6 May 1932
    - Julie (1), 21 April 1932
    - Ned (1), 13 January 1932
    - Phillip K. (1), 3 February 1932
    - Illegible (1), 10 January 1908
    - “ (to Mrs. Quin) (1), 18 November ?
- Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Taylor to unknown recipient, undated
- Bills, contract (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Plays and stories by Taylor (Box 2, Folder 1-12)
- Music by Taylor (Box 2, Folder 13; Box: 3, Folder: 1-2)
  - Dance of the Birds
  - Darlene
  - Fairy's Song
  - Good Morning Ladies
  - Hilo Somebody
  - Honey
  - The Hoodoo Gal
  - How Beautiful Upon the Mountains I'm A' Goin' Away In Thy Love Again I Live Jesus Only
  - The Joy O' Living! from Sylvelia
  - King Hakow
  - Love the Conqueror - Fairy Chorus
  - Love's Coronation
  - A Lover Bold
  - Lullaby
  - Mignonette
  - My Ever Lovin' Baby
  - My Rosieline - words by Marie LeRoy
  - Water Babies
  - Old Songs of Long Ago - a medley written for the Vanderbilt Glee Club
  - The One I Adore and The Moon Path (by Adams & Beach)
  - Page's Song - from Charlemagne (arrangements for various instruments)
  - Ragtime Romeo Sally Brown
  - Sometimes and A White Rose
  - A Song of the Road - words from poem by James Whitcomb Riley
  - Song of Summer - words by Will Allen Dromgoole
  - Thou Art the Theme Tinker Belle
  - Twinkle and Blinky - from Star Children Stories by Serita MacLeary
  - Wild Goose Shanty
- Music by Taylor (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Workbooks, scrapbooks, notebooks (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous holograph notes (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Holograph worknotes (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Programs of plays in which Taylor appeared (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Photographs - Taylor (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Photographs - Taylor (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Photographs - Theatre and stage personalities (Box 4, Folder 2-6)
  - Adams, Maude (3) (Box 4)
  - Allan, Maud (1) (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Mary (1) (Box 4)
  - Anglin, Margaret (4) (Box 4)
  - Barry, Eleanor (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Barrymore, Eleanor (1) (Box 4)
  - Barrymore, John (1) (Box 4)
  - Barrymore, John, Jr. (1) (Box 4)
  - Bates, Blanche (1) (Box 4)
  - Bellew, Kyrie (1) (Box 4)
  - Benson, F. R. (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Bernhardt, Sarah (1) (Box 4)
  - Blimm, Holbrook (2) (Box 4)
  - Campbell, Mrs. Pat (2) (Box 4)
  - Cayvan, Miss (1) (Box 4)
  - Cheatham, Kitty (3) (Box 4)
  - Clayburgh, ? (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Coburn, Charles (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Coghlan, Rose (3) 1 autographed (Box 4)
  - Daly, Arnold (1) (Box 4)
  - Davenport, Fanny (1) (Box 4)
  - Del Rio, Dolores (1) (Box 4)
  - Douglas, Charles E. (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Duncan, Jean (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Edeson, Robert (1) (Box 4)
  - Elliott, Maxime (1) (Box 4)
  - Farnum, Dustin (1) % (Box 4)
  - Favershara, William (1) (Box 4)
  - Fiske, Mrs. (1) (Box 4)
  - Frederick, Pauline (7) 3 autographed (Box 4)
  - Garitza, Marie (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Gillette, William (1) (Box 4)
  - GilIman, Mabel (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Gorden, Mary (1) (Box 4)
  - Gresham, Herbert (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Griffith, David (1) (Box 4)
  - Haramill, Hugh (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Hammond, Virginia (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Hickman, Bessie (Mrs. Howard) (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Hickman, Howard (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Hitchcock, Raymond (2) (Box 4)
  - Irving, Henry (2) (Box 4)
  - Irwin, May (1) (Box 4)
  - Jewett, Henry (2) (Box 4)
  - Keenan, Frank (1) (Box 4)
  - Langtry, Lily (1) (Box 4)
  - Laurener, Edmund (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Lewis, Iva (2) 1 autographed (Box 4)
  - Loftus, Cecilia (1) (Box 4)
  - MacDonaId, Christie (1) (Box 4)
  - MacDowell, George J. (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Mamillus, Grenvilie (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Mansfield, Richard (2) (Box 4)
  - Mantel, Robert (1) (Box 4)
  - Marlowe, Julia (2) (Box 4)
  - Mart inde 1, Ed & Jane (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Miller, Henry (1) (Box 4)
  - Modjeska, Madame (1) (Box 4)
  - Morris, Lucy B. (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Naz imova (1) (Box 4)
  - Nesbit, Evelyn (5) (Box 4)
  - Nethersole, Olga (1) (Box 4)
  - Nijinsky (1) (Box 4)
  - O'Neil, Nance (1) (Box 4)
  - Patterson, Elizabeth (1) (Box 4)
  - Pavlova (6) (Box 4)
  - Perugini, Signor (1) (Box 4)
  - Powers, Eugene (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Rehan, Ada (1) (Box 4)
  - Reicher, Hedwig (2) (Box 4)
  - Ritchie, Adele (1) (Box 4)
  - Roshanara (2) (Box 4)
  - Russell, Lillian (1) (Box 4)
  - Salvini (2) (Box 4)
  - Scheff, Fritzi (1) (Box 4)
  - Schoolar, Norma (2) autographed (Box 4)
  - Sherer, Norma (3) (Box 4)
  - Sothern, E. H. (1) (Box 4)
  - Starling, Lynn (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Stone, Florence (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Sunderland, Pet (1) (Box 4)
  - Talioferro, Mabel (1) (Box 4)
  - Taylor, Laurette (3) (Box 4)
  - Tellefen, Lou (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Terry, Ellen (3) (Box 4)
  - Terry, Phyllis Nelson (1) (Box 4)
  - Valentino, Rudolph (1) (Box 4)
  - Vuray, Ruth (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Wallace-Hopper, Edna (2) autographed (Box 4)
  - Warfield, David (3) (Box 4)
  - Washburns, Charles C. (1) autographed (Box 4)
  - Wilson, Francis (1) (Box 4)
  - Wilson, Katherine (4) 3 autographed (Box 4)
  - Woodruff, Henry (1) (Box 4)
  - Yergin, Sonja (1) autographed (Box 4)
- Promptbooks - Icebound (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Promptbooks - Shakespeare (4) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Play scripts by others (Box 5, Folder 3-21)
- Radio scripts (Box 5, Folder 22-25)
- Radio scripts (Box 6, Folder 1-7)
- "Poems and Songs", WSM Radio show materials (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
  - All Through the Night Asthore (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Blow, Blow, Thou Winter's Wind (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - By the Bend of the River (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Down in the Forest (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dreams (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Forgotten (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Good to Forgive (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hark! Hark! the Lark (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Harp that Once Through Tara's Halls The Herb Forgetfulness Hindoo Song (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - I'll Sing Thee Songs of Araby In Bygone Days Kashmiri Song Largo (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Less than the Dust (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Loch Lomond (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - No Night There (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Oh Fair, Oh Sweet and Holy (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Road to Yesterday (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Song of Songs (2) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Three-part solo with contralto, bass, and tenor parts (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Till I Wake (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Unmindful of the Roses (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Who is Sylvia? (2) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - All in the April Evening (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Beloved, It Is Morn (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - For the Beauty of the Earth (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Jean (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The Lord's Prayer The Lost Chord (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - My Moonlight Madonna (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Near the Cross Her Vigil Keeping (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Still, Still With Thee (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Summer Longings (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Take My Life and Let It Be (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Where My Caravan Has Rested (Box 6, Folder 9)
- "Poems and Songs," WSM Radio show materials (Box 7, Folder 1-7)
  - As My Dear Old Mother (3) A Banjo Song (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Believe Me, If All Those Endearing Young Charms (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Blessed Are the Pure in Heart (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Blue Are Her Eyes (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Clouds (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dedication (3) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - For You Alone (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Home on the Range (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Home, Sweet Home (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Just A-Wearyin' for You (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Kathleen Mavourneen (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Massa's in the Cold Ground (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - None But the Lonely Heart (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - A Plantation Hymn (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Serenade (Keeping Watch O'er My Maiden) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Serenade (Softly Through the Night) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Serenade (Thro' the Leaves) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Star (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Steal Away (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Trees (2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Annie Laurie (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - At Dawning (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Beaten Biscuit (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Blue are Her Eyes (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Brooklet (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Calm as the Night (2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Do You Remember? (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Drink to Me Only with Thine Eyes Duna (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Estrellita (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Evening Fair (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Flow Gently S t Afton (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - For All Eternity (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Forgotten (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Four Leaf Clover (2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - From the Land of the Sky-Blue Water (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Goin' Home (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Gypsy Trail (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hear Mel Ye Winds and Waves! (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Hills of Home (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - I Love Thee (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - If (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - If I Can Live (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - In the Gloaming (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - In the Luxembourg Gardens (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - In a Persian Garden (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - In the Time of Roses (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Into the Woods (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Last Hour (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Last Night (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lead Kindly Light (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lingering, Lonely Rose (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Little Lady of the Moon (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Little Man (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - My Desire (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - My Old Kentucky Home, Good Night (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - O Dry Those Tears! (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - O Irraingard! (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Old Black Joe (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Old Road (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - One Fleeting Hour (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - A Red, Red Rose (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Roilin' Home (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sence You Went Away (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Silver Ring (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Smilin' Through (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - A Spirit Flower (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sunset (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sylvia (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Tears of God (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The Temple Bells (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - There is a Land (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Till I Wake (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Twilight on the Trail (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Where Cross the Crowded Ways of Life (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Where'er You Walk (3) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - While My Heart is Singing to You (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - The World is Waiting for the Sunrise (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - The Good Green Acres of Home (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - In the County of Davidson (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Jesus Christ (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - May Day Carol (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - The Mystery of Song (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Responses (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - A Thought Like Music (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Danny Dever Dearest Believe (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Do Not Go, My Love Elegy (2) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - An Evening Prayer (3) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - The Heart Bowed Down (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - The Hills of Home (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - It Singeth Low in Every Heart (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Long, Long Ago (2) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mah Lindy Lou (2) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Passing By (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Watchman Tell Us of the Night (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Above the Hills (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - A Brown Bird Singing (2) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Carry Me Back to the Lone Prairie (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The Christian Life (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Down in the Forest (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Flow Gently, Sweet Afton (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Home to My Blue Hills (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Little Grey Home in the West (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The Lord's Prayer (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - A Perfect Day (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - A Plantation Hymn (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Saviour, Hear Us, We Pray (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - A Spirit Flower (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sweet Hour of Prayer (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - A Thought Like Music (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Absent (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Beneath the Cross of Jesus (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bird Songs at Eventide (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Blind Ploughman (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Do Not Go, My Love (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Home on the Range (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - I Love Life (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Iris (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Lonesome Road (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Monotone (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Ninety and Nine (2) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - None But the Lonely Heart (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - The Old Road (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Think Love of Me (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Uncle Rome (2) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Friend 0' Mine (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - I Am Fate! (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Last Hour (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Massa's in the Cold Ground (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Nobody Knows the Trouble I See (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Pauper's Drive (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pilgrim's Song (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Santa Lucia (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Poems by others (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous music by others (Box 7, Folder 9)
- John Barrymore note to wardrobe mistress (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Newspaper clippings - Taylor (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Newspaper clippings - Nashville (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Newspaper clippings - Barrymores (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
- Newspaper clippings - Theatre and stage (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
- Newspaper clippings - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
- Playbills and Programs (Box 8, Folder 4-13)
- Playbills and Programs (Box 9, Folder 1-14)
- Playbills and Programs, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Printed Materials - Drama and Theatre (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Printed Materials - Lead Kindly Light by Cardinal Newman (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Printed Materials - Menus, German marks (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Printed Materials - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Printed Materials - Nashville (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Printed Materials - The 1915 Mode and speeches by Robert L. Taylor (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Printed Materials - Shakespeare materials (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Printed Materials - The Thespian Preceptor published by J. Roach (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Printed Materials - World's Columbian Exposition, 1892 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Oversize - Photographs and Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Pencil Drawing - unidentified (1) (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Hand-tinted - unidentified (2) (Box 12)
  - Photographs - Identified
    - Armstrong, Will– autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Barrymore, John – autographed, 1922 (Box 12)
    - Barrymore, John – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Bori, Lucretia – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Burrus, Jefferson D. – autographed (Box 12)
    - Carter, Mrs. Leslie, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Caruso, n.d. (Box 12)
    - D'Auvrieyies, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Doyle, Miriam – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Ellsler, Effie, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Faversham, William, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Fox, Della, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Fuller, Rosalind – autographed, 1923 (Box 12)
    - Gilbert, William – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Goodrich, Edna, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Goodrich, Edna, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Gould, Rita – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Gould, Rita – autographed, 1928 (Box 12)
    - Hall, Laura Nelson – autographed, 1899 (Box 12)
    - Hamilton, Alice – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Hughie, Margarite, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Illington, Margaret, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Jode', Fran – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Jonani, Irene – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Keene, Doris – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Kern, Cecil – autographed, 1918 (Box 12)
    - LaVarre, Marie – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - LaVerne, Lucille – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Lawlor, Andrew J. Jr – autographed (Box 12)
    - Lewis, Charlotte – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Lewis, Ida – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Lo-Ve' & Wilber – autographed, 1918 (Box 12)
    - MacDowell, Irene – autographed, 1907 (Box 12)
    - MacDowell, Melbourne – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Martinnice, Edward B – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - McDonald, Christie, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Moore, Grace – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Nijinsky, Waslav, n.d. (Box 12)
    - O'Neil, Nance – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - O'Neil, Nance - autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - O'Neil, Nance – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - O'Toole, Gwendolen – autographed, 1918 (Box 12)
    - Patten, Henry W. – autographed, 1913 (Box 12)
    - Pavlova, Anna, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Power, Tyrone – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Power, Tyrone, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Rich, Irene – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Russell, Lillian – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Simmons, Ernest R. – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Sothern, E. H, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Sothern, E. H. & Julia Marlowe, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Sothern, E. H. & Julia Marlowe, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Stephens, Emily, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Stove, Ren – autographed, 1909 (Box 12)
    - Teel, Olive – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Vesey, Minnie Crudup – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Vesey, Minnie Crudup, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Warburton, John – autographed, 1929 (Box 12)
    - Warren, Bessie – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
    - Waters, Hadley – autographed, 1919 (Box 12)
    - West, Mae – autographed, n.d. (Box 12)
  - Photographs - unidentified (11) (Box 12)